Good morning, Herbalife!
Great to be here.
Sunday morning.
So I'll tell you a quick story
before we bring out someone very, very special.
So, first of all, what about Jerry and Mark?
Was that fantastic or what?
Wow. Fantastic.
You know, it's interesting.
In the company, I always say to
the executives, go back and watch Mark.
Because we're not doing anything differently
today than what was his original dream.
It's what the Chairman's Club taught me.
It's where the roots of our company are.
And every word he said there holds true today.
It's pretty amazing.
Alright, so quick story, then
I'll bring out our next guest.
Quick story, then I'll bring out our next guest.
See if we can try that again.
My first extravaganza was in June, I think.
In Las Vegas, 2003.
Was it June of 2000?
And I had to get the family adjusted.
How did that happen?
Well, first of all, we had
thisиком of a couple of business.
And then I said, will
you just do me a remission?
And we had the idea that I wanted to
do this film kind of in December of 2010,
so that people could follow two or three years.
And we went straight and did it.
And then we decided to do this film and take
care of the little child that was on the film.
And the person that was doing this film was you.
And I was one of them all the time.
I needed to be with them.
And we didn't have time.
We had weapons.
when we're together on Sundays we follow the same path
and so when I said to Mary well I'm not going
to you know be here and we went through the
schedule and she said boy that's a that's a lot
of Sundays you're not going to be here and I said
don't worry about it you know we'll make up for it
and I'll spend a little extra time and she was
kind of more worried about the fact that we were
breaking down a family tradition that had lived in
both of our families a long time and then on
Sunday in Las Vegas Jim Rohn came out and
he and he spoke and I was sitting side stage
listening to Jim and I was so tremendously moved by
the spirit that this guy is by the human being
that he is by his words his compassion
his leadership his ability to touch on your mind
and your soul and many of
those words that we heard from Mark
may have been about integrity but they were also
about living a better life and being a better
human being and living for the whole and
creating opportunity around more than just the individual
and bringing people in with a bigger heart and so
Jim was doing the same things and he was on stage
and I was tremendously moved by Jim bought
his books and his tapes and have now become
a very good friend of Jim's I hope he feels
the same way about me that I feel about him
because I see Jim as one of those
kind of spiritual signposts in my life someone
to emulate live up to so Jim got
done and I couldn't help but I jumped on
the cell phone and called my wife and I
said don't worry honey I said I've been
to church today yeah I've been to the
church of Jim Rohn today and so you know so you
know and and it worked and as you know our buddy
Jim who was Mark's mentor and in in was
has been in the direct selling business since the
1950s Jim is a pioneer and Jim's gone through
you know some health issues lately but he's all ours
still and man do we love Jim Rohn don't we I
mean he is just something special so we we we love Jim
enough to have him here today so
let's welcome Jim Rohn onto our stage today
we're going to pilot our
right so we use of the
Google Maps Dog Trips
all right let's do that
work
better
and
so
Gary, how are you doing?
I got the chocolates.
Hi.
Wow.
Korea.
Nice to see you.
I love you.
Fantastic.
Wow, I love you.
Nice to see you.
Incredible.
Hey, Mario.
Tell everybody hello for me in Korea.
Okay?
Nice to see you.
Wow.
Pleasure.
Hi.
Nice to see you again.
Wow.
Good to see you.
Tell everybody hello.
Wow.
Thank you.
How are you?
Good.
Fantastic.
I love all of you.
Thank you very much.
I'm happy to be here.
Hey, you guys.
Wow.
Hi, Brian.
How are you?
Good to see you.
Sarah said, I talked to Marcus Lehman.
I talked to Alan Lorenz.
Good to see you.
Wow.
Hey, John.
Give me that chair.
Give me this chair.
Right here, Jeff?
Yeah.
Here we are.
I'm going to say hello to my friends here.
Hey, good to see you.
How's Dallas?
Very good.
Fantastico.
Hey, good to see you again.
Wow.
Good to see you.
Thank you.
Wow.
Viva Mexico.
Hey, young man.
Hey, John.
It's only been 29 years.
How are you doing?
Good to see you.
Marcus.
Isn't this something?
It's Ben.
How are you doing?
Hi, Ben.
Nice to see you.
Yeah, it's great to see you.
Yeah.
Hey, Michael.
How are you doing?
How's Madrid?
Madrid, Madrid.
Waiting for you.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, fantastic.
Leslie.
Wow.
I love you.
What a day, huh?
Incredible.
Tell everybody in Europe hello for me.
We do.
Okay.
I'm getting better every day.
Fantastic.
Amartat.
So good to see you.
Wow.
How goes?
How's Israel?
Very good.
Doing good?
Yeah.
Okay.
We do better.
All right.
Thank you.
Muchas gracias, everybody.
Well, what an honor it
is for me to be here.
So, I wish I could kiss you all.
But we don't have that much time.
But thanks for the welcome everybody,
thank you, I appreciate it very much.
When I first got ill, I was weighing, I
don't know, 123 pounds. So I started on three shakes
a day, plus all the food I could
possibly eat, I didn't have an appetite. And thanks
to my daughter, thanks to Sarah, I
started gaining weight, got my appetite back, and
I've gained over 30 pounds. 30 pounds.
Now I'm back to two shakes a day, so I
can lose a pound or two, right? A little too much.
But when I started gaining weight, I started
getting better. And then of course all this
time, Mike McKee and Evie and the staff
at Herbalife Home Office, they were all saying
they'd been sending me the emails, and the
letters and the videos and the DVDs, just overwhelming
from all around the world. And I want
you to know that your thoughts and prayers helped
me to get well.
How it all started.
And my thoughts and prayers went
out to you this past year.
That the good Lord would bless you with good people,
help you build a strong organization,
touch the people that needed to be touched.
I need a calculation, Alan, and
you can get it for me later.
How many people are in the 70 countries?
It has to be maybe 2 billion or more.
At least?
Maybe three?
Let's jot that down.
Herbalife now is represented in 70 countries,
which gives us a market of over 3 billion people.
Now we have some more countries to go, I'm sure,
but right now,
the market is 3 billion.
So guess what?
No matter how much business we do, we're behind.
Babies are being born faster
than we can sell Herbalife products.
Every new customer we get, there's
three more babies somewhere in the world.
So the market is forever.
And the market is going
to be a challenge, that is.
In 70 countries, a market of 3 billion people.
So the key now is for all of you, especially
having come to receive your honors here at this special occasion,
our job now is to build the organizations that
can reach more and more of the 3 billion people.
They're going to be overweight until you get there.
They're going to have a long list of health problems.
They're going to have a long list
of health problems until you get there.
Until you get there, some people are only
earning, in some countries, a dollar a day.
A dollar a day.
And that's all they're going to earn, is a
dollar a day, until you and your organization arrives,
knocking on their door, handing out a flyer, saying hello.
They're going to be waiting for you.
The family is going to have all
kinds of problems until you get there.
People are going to be in despair
until you arrive. You and your organization.
So the three billion are waiting and
our job is almost overwhelming. I don't know
how Michael Johnson as the CEO takes
care of making sure all the products are
now in 70 countries. I don't know how
he does it. Guess what the job is called?
Impossible. If we were to put an ad
in the paper to replace the CEO we would
say, if you're interested in
an impossible job please call. Michael
you're doing a fabulous job. I love you.
Impossible. But he gets it done and
represents us so well. It's just been
fantastic. Mark got us off to a good
start. First 50 countries but now 20 more
and Michael the last what almost
six years has really stepped in these
incredible responsibility shoes.
And now it takes care of us so well. But
we've got a big job to do. Here's a good
note for you. Mark wanted to create for
us a place. Not necessarily just like a
room. A room is a place. This hotel is
a place. But he wanted a place and at first
he called it a family. A
family place where everybody felt like
of the family but now it's gotten bigger
than that we now meet in great places
around the world and have 18,000 people that's
a place so the note for you to
take is the place is the people
the place is the distributors the place is
you and me a place where people can
come hear a story use the products change
their health start blessing their family and
a place where they can start earning
money that training that mark gave is just
as valid today when I see it on the
video as it was when he gave it
back all those years ago in person just start
you
and start expanding thinking we've got
three billion people to reach so you've
got to reach your share chairman's club
members you've got to reach your share
president's team you've got to reach
your share tabulator team members you've
got to reach your share start expanding
your organization go on a little bit
more of a fast-track recruiting program
because we're behind we're behind the population
is increasing faster than we can possibly get to them
they're complaining business now in America
for 29 years guess what there's
more overweight people in America now than
when we started 29 years ago so we
are behind we are half möjment
behind another people
more overweight people now than when we
started 29 years ago which means we're behind
as fast as we can run we stay behind because
the market is so big the market is so ready
the market is so available and now expanding
around the world in 70 countries you can imagine
the task we have trying to reach all of the
people so in this unique place that mark has created
where we arrive on special occasions like this
here's the note your story inside the herbal life
story is what's important so here's a
phrase master the testimonials that's what mark was
all about creating testimonials early testimonials someone says
i've only been here a short period of
time here's what's happened to my health
here's what's happened to my family here's what's
happened to my
individual
i've started making money already early testimonials
so be a master of the testimonials
because two things really especially at this level for
all of you are important number one the training
mark wanted the finest training in the world and
you're doing that or we wouldn't be in 70 countries
doing what three billion headed for four and
we'll soon have the magic number mark wanted
five billion so you're doing that
and you're doing that now you're doing your
job but what's important is the training the information
number one the training is very important
because it's the most important in this life
but here's what goes along with the
training the testimonials so master the testimonials
the testimonials the testimonials reach the heart
the trade the training reaches the head
so you want to reach the mind the head
so people understand have answers but you also want
to reach the heart so let's go out with a
new determination to reach the heart the heart is the heart
somebody so that they're stronger
mentally, can make better decisions about
joining Herbalife, about staying, about
becoming a part of this wonderful
adventure that's on its way, and
then inspire them with the testimonials. Okay.
I still love to sit and hear
the testimonials. Some people say, well the
Chairman's Club are way up here. But
what what inspires me is their testimonials
one more time. The Little London
meetings, Alan, right? The Little London meetings.
All those years ago, driving around
in your Mercedes. I just, the testimonials
are so fantastic. Here's where we
started. The Little London meetings. And then
where did we go to? Alberts Hall, what
is that called? Royal Albert Hall. One of the
greatest
venues in all of London and probably in
all of the world. Royal Albert Hall. There
was Alan, there was Mark Hughes, some of
you were there, and guess who else was
there? Jim Rohn. Jim Rohn was there. Wow.
In the Royal Albert Hall. From the
little London meetings to the Royal Albert
Hall. I'm just stunned by it all.
I'm just overwhelmed by it all. The testimonials,
what you've been through, the things you
overcame to arrive here, and what all of
you have been through. Guess what I
wish we could do today? Hear everybody's
testimonial one more time.
So let's just stay another two or three days, okay?
That suits me. I love to just sit
around and hug and kiss and tell the
testimonials one more time. Wow. The stuff
we've been through, all of the obstacles
we overcame, people prayed for us from
around the world. When I started thinking
about people are praying for me
all around the world, it was absolutely
overwhelming. And all of us send
our prayers to our organization, to Herbal
Life and 70 countries. Pray for Herbal
Life. Pray for the distributors that go
out and knock on doors. Pray for those
who hand out flyers. Pray for those who
are just getting started and they're scared
to death and don't know what to do.
Let's pray. Let's pray.
Let's pray for everybody out there.
Your prayers were magic for me and
it'll be magic for everybody you pray for.
You can't imagine what an experience this is for me.
I've had a real challenge with my health.
But...
And I had to miss the
extravaganza. I was really sorry about that.
And Mexico. I had to miss Mexico extravaganza.
Wow. Thank you.
They had 18,000 and I wanted
so bad to be there with Sarah.
And I was so sorry.
I was so sorry.
I couldn't make it.
But I called in and said hello.
And I also called in for
the American, the North America extravaganza.
I don't know what region this whole region entails.
And it was as good for me as
it was for the people when I called in.
I can't tell you how much I love you.
That's going to take a lot more years.
So I'm going to live a lot more years.
Thank you.
So I can do that.
So let's accelerate our recruiting program.
Because people are going to be in the room.
And I'm going to be in the room.
Because people are going to be in the
dark until you come and bring them some light.
People are going to be unhappy until
you come and bring them a Herbalife fiesta.
People are going to be unrecognized until
you come and get them inside this family.
And shower them with recognition.
Shower them with handshakes and hugs and kisses.
And telling them you can do it.
If we can do it,
come on, you can do it.
So they're out there.
Three billion are out there.
Waiting patiently.
Waiting for you to come.
So let's accelerate our recruiting program.
Get good at doing your part of the training.
And some of you that are starting your leadership training, you know, when
someone asks you to participate in a meeting, give your testimonial, always say yes.
So repeat that after me.
Always say yes.
Everybody.
Every little thing they want you to do.
Would you stand by the door
and welcome people as they come in?
Say yes.
Would you shake hands with the
people that are brand new here tonight?
Say yes.
Every little thing, say yes.
Because it's not just learning
to give a good training program.
It's learning to shake hands.
It's learning to say hello to someone.
It's learning to say welcome.
Part of the culture of Herbalife.
That's it.
Mark started it 29 years ago.
And that is the culture.
Make yourself at home.
You're going to hear a fantastic story.
And if they're brand new,
say you're going to make it.
If they say I haven't made any sales and I've been here
four days already, say the fifth day is always the magic day.
That's Mark Hustyle.
If you had some challenges last week, this next
week is going to be your best week ever.
No telling who will join if
you'll just keep doing what you're doing.
That's the magic of Herbalife.
Always say yes.
Master the testimonials.
Learn to give good training.
Informal.
Just a few points.
Here's what Herbalife's all about.
A place where you can come in from the cold.
A place where you can come and get around people
who will cheer you on every step of the way.
A place where you can get healthy and get your family
healthy and start contacting your relatives and people you care about.
Get them healthy.
A place where you can start earning money.
Change your whole financial cycle.
First start paying your bills.
You're both on time.
Finally you've got some extra
money and you start to give.
Casa Herbalife.
Just remember Mark Hughes.
Remember the simple story.
The testimonials.
And remember the challenge.
We've got a big job.
And it looks like right now we're behind.
Behind, yes.
So we've got to run to
catch up the best we can.
I think that's enough from me.
I love you all more than I can possibly say.
And thanks to my Sarah who has helped take care
of me as well as my daughter for the last year.
Thank you Sarah.
I love you dearly.
And thanks.
Thank you.
Thanks to the home office staff.
Thank, where's Luigi?
Thanks to Luigi who filled in for me.
And Jack Kavulich.
You know.
I had to throw my schedule away for a while.
I couldn't travel, couldn't fly.
And Jack and Luigi picked it up and started traveling.
So thanks to Jack and
Luigi for filling in for me.
Wow.
Well I could talk all day.
But I think I'm going to have to go.
I think this is enough.
I embrace all of you.
With my heart and soul.
We are fulfilling Mark's dream.
And that's what I've wanted to
do for the last 29 years.
And in these next few years, let's really grow.
Let's really accelerate.
Let's expand.
Let's reach out.
Let's touch somebody.
With the magic that we've got.
So thank you all for coming.
Thanks for your incredible welcome.
I want to spend the rest
of my life with all of you.
God bless.
Thanks to all of you
for being so kind to me.
I'm going to go now.
Have a nice day in the world.
Bye bye.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021